http://www.gracehill.org/privacy-policy

Home PRIVACY POLICY Grace Hill Settlement House is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Grace Hill Settlement House website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Grace Hill Settlement House website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONGrace Hill Settlement House may collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Grace Hill Settlement House also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Grace Hill Settlement House. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Grace Hill Settlement House for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Grace Hill Settlement House Website.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Grace Hill Settlement House public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Grace Hill Settlement House does not read any of your private online communications.Grace Hill Settlement House encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Grace Hill Settlement House so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Grace Hill Settlement House is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Grace Hill Settlement House and Grace Hill Settlement House family of websites.USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONGrace Hill Settlement House collects and uses your personal information to operate the Grace Hill Settlement House website and deliver the services you have requested. Grace Hill Settlement House also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Grace Hill Settlement House and its affiliates. Grace Hill Settlement House may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Grace Hill Settlement House does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Grace Hill Settlement House may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Grace Hill Settlement House may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Grace Hill Settlement House, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Grace Hill Settlement House does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Grace Hill Settlement House keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Grace Hill Settlement House, in order to determine what Grace Hill Settlement House services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Grace Hill Settlement House to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.The Grace Hill Settlement House website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Grace Hill Settlement House or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Grace Hill Settlement House; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Grace Hill Settlement House, or the public.USE OF COOKIESThe Grace Hill Settlement House website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Grace Hill Settlement House pages, or register with Grace Hill Settlement House site or services, a cookie helps Grace Hill Settlement House to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Grace Hill Settlement House website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Grace Hill Settlement House features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Grace Hill Settlement House services or websites you visit.SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONGrace Hill Settlement House secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Grace Hill Settlement House secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENTGrace Hill Settlement House will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Grace Hill Settlement House encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Grace Hill Settlement House is protecting your information.CONTACT INFORMATIONGrace Hill Settlement House welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Grace Hill Settlement House has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Grace Hill Settlement House at info@gracehillsettlement.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.Grace Hill Settlement House welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Grace Hill Settlement House has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Grace Hill Settlement House at info@gracehillsettlement.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Water Tower Hub Grace Hill’s one-stop support center provides academic, economic and community development programs to uplift the College Hill neighborhood.
Volunteers From Fortune 500 companies to grandmothers giving back, Grace Hill offers volunteer opportunities to all who want to change St. Louis for the better.
Head Start We provide over 300 children each year with best-in-class early childhood education, focusing on social/emotional development, community learning and family advancement.
Key Partners No one can boost a neighborhood alone. Grace Hill partners with residents and important institutions like St. Louis Community Credit Union for long-term impact.
United Way For 90 years, the United Way has supported our most critical work, reaching families where they are and providing strategic stepping stones to their well-being. Grace Hill Health Centers is now Affinia Healthcare.You can find them at www.affiniahealthcare.org or by calling 314.814.8700.
Looking for Grace Hill Health Centers?You can find them at www.gracehill.org or by calling 314.814.8700. ×
